janae breunig

CREATIVE DESIGNER

Ouluth, MN, USA

www.janaebreunig.com

🔀 janaebreunig@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/janaebreunig/

715.651.7437

UI designer with over 10 years of experience in print design. Experienced in graphic design, typography, layout, logo design, illustration, UX & UI processes and branding systems within both large and small in-house marketing teams as well as client based work.

skills

- User Interface Design
- Branding
- Typography
- · Color Theory
- Layout
- Illustration
- Logo Design
- User Personas
- Usability Analysis
- User Testing Interviews
- User Research
- Wireframing
- Prototyping

tools

- Adobe Creative Suite
 InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop. XD
- Figma
- Adobe Workfront
- MS Office Suite
- Google Workspace
- Basecamp

education

UI Design Certificate with specialization in Frontend Development for Designers CareerFoundry

January 2023 - December 2023

Bachelor of Arts | Major: Graphic Design

University of Wisconsin - Eau Claire September 2008 - May 2013

work experience

Graphic Design Specialist

maurices • August 2019 - Present • Duluth, MN

- Collaborated with partners to develop promotional signage for over 900 retail stores across the US and Canada.
- Translated marketing briefs from the operations team into effective visual solutions to help drive sales.
- Worked with teammates to bring seasonal concepts to life, and showcase product newness to customers in exciting ways.
- Partnered with Visual Merchandising team to test proposed design solutions in a mock-store setting to ensure execution worked as we envisioned, as well as test for any potential issues with store compliance.
- Prepare all print collateral for stores for print per specifications from different vendors and release, then proof and quality check final prints to make sure they are up to standards.

Brand Graphics Coordinator

Whole Foods Co-op • August 2018 - August 2019 • Duluth, MN

- Worked within a marketing team to help increase brand visibility and community involvement.
- Created weekly sales signage and other promotional material, as well as branded larger internal events to help drive sales and motivate staff.
- Tabled at community events to engage and educate the public on the benefits of ownership and encourage relationships with community partners.
- Worked with multiple departments to fulfill any design needs.

Graphic Designer

Volume One and The Local Store • August 2014 - July 2018 • Eau Claire, WI

- Created print and web ads for 50+ local businesses spanning all types of industries, including dining & hospitality, events, service industries, wellness, pet care, retail, and any others that would come through.
- Worked with multiple departments to create biweekly publication focused on arts, music and culture in the Chippewa Valley through ad design, feature layouts, editorial illustrations, and other various projects.
- Helped plan, create designs for, and execute a variety of large and small scale community events including the Sounds Like Summer Concert Series, Restaurant Week, April Fools Pillow Fight, The Best Night, and many others.
- Collaborated with community artists by both directing the Volume One Gallery and procuring cover art for our magazine.
- Worked with small committee to confer about potential new store products, products that should be designed in-house, and the general direction and future of the retail space.

Graphic Designer

E&G Franchise Systems, Inc. • April 2013 - August 2014 • Eau Claire, WI

- Created promotional material for individual franchise locations to fulfill their specific needs.
- Worked with an In-House design team to create material that is true to the corporate identity system already in place.
- Contributed to a marketing team to ideate new strategies to move the company's brand forward for both B2B as well as B2C situations.